<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Agile on From The Front</title>
    <link>/tags/agile/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Agile on From The Front</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/tags/agile/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous reteaming: planning day workshop - Enabling constraints</title>
      <link>/blog/continuous-reteaming-qplanning-enabling-constraints/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 02 Sep 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/continuous-reteaming-qplanning-enabling-constraints/</guid>
      <description>In Continuous reteaming: planning day workshop - Achievements and target outcomes, we&amp;rsquo;ve seen how to start building alignment by sharing both the achievements and the target outcomes for the next quarter. It is a worthy exercise in itself, which should improve collaboration and reduce waste. However, we are a long way from having a new team structure for the next quarter. So how do you ensure that people self-select into teams that are not entirely crazy?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous reteaming: planning day workshop - Achievements and target outcomes</title>
      <link>/blog/continuous-reteaming-qplanning-intro-and-presentations/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 14 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/continuous-reteaming-qplanning-intro-and-presentations/</guid>
      <description>In Continuous Reteaming and Self-Selection, I gave a general overview of the system of work I experimented with for 18 months. I will now detail various parts, starting with the planning day.
Planning day format Our planning day is essential to achieve our goals: self-selection and self-organisation. It follows the following structure:
 Agenda &amp;amp; intro to the day Last quarter achievements Target outcomes Presentation of the enabling constraints Iterations to form the teams Broadcast of the plan  Agenda &amp;amp; intro This workshop is going to be new for at least some of your colleagues.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuous Reteaming and Self-Selection</title>
      <link>/blog/continuous-reteaming-and-self-selection/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 07 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/continuous-reteaming-and-self-selection/</guid>
      <description>In the book Drive, Dan Pink proposes that the 3 sources of intrinsic motivation are autonomy, mastery and purpose. In my experience, our system of work is rarely aligned with that. More often than not:
 You are assigned to a project by your manager, You follow a prescribed methodology like Scrum or Kanban (or have none at all and no forum to reflect), You have a long list of requirements that sound quite disconnected from any tangible business impact (possibly written by a PO/PM, sometimes they may even let you talk to the customer ;-)).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>4 years of squad health check</title>
      <link>/blog/4-years-of-squad-health-check/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 13 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blog/4-years-of-squad-health-check/</guid>
      <description>Earlier in January, we ran our squad health check for Q4 2018. We invited an observer that was keen to discover the activity, and see if it would be beneficial for his own team. We had a quick chat at the end of the hour about my experience as a manager, and it suddenly hit me that I had been running squad health checks for the better part of the last 4 years&amp;hellip; Time flies!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>